Threatened by a ruthless demon, humanity was on the brink of destruction.
All seemed lost until a lone mage stepped forward and took up the fight.
After his triumph, he was hailed as the Wizard King, and his story became legend.
At the end of the Star Festival, King Clover made a momentous announcement.
We have located the Midnight Sun's Hideout.
You will be pleased to know that we're preparing to launch a full-scale counter-attack of our own.
And to do so, we plan to gather the absolute cream of the crop of our Magic Knight squads,
allowing us to assemble the most elite team imaginable.
And that unit will be called the Royal Knights.
The time has come for all of the Magic Knights to face the test
that will determine their eligibility to join the Kingdom's most select team.
-
알고
See you later...
We'll be right back.
What a hassle and right when I finally get back from my expedition to you're on the verge of obstructing official business
as a magic knight i'll be forced to punish you for that do you have any idea who this is you're in the presence of zarfs lugner vice captain of the purple orcas if it weren't for this man's strength and virtue the purple orcas could never have accomplished as much he is the saint of pure ice what would i know about that fancy pants saint of pure ice i don't see any ice around here if you ask me he should be the saint of carcasses rotting in the mud how dare you and
you why are you singing his praises as though you're some kind of pathetic little lapdog what's the matter is your master too stupid to introduce himself without your help official business you said
you big wigs sure have it made don't you using pretty words to control anybody who's unlucky enough to rub you the wrong way
go ahead be my guest use that magic you're so proud of and teach me a lesson for justice
we know you're itching for a power trip mr vice captain of the goon squad i've heard quite enough
words of contempt for the magic knights i won't have it now taste my magic and repent ice magic ice slicer
that was the saint of pure ice sad poor guy must be crushed i bet it stings to lose to someone like me
this magic knight robe is wasted on a wuss like you
now then i wonder if anyone else needs an ego check
it's the big royal knights exam i don't know what to expect but whatever it is i'll be ready
finally a chance to show the kingdom what i can really do
oh dear i know you're excited sir but even that small amount of power can be a problem for the people around you
do you think you could be a little less enthusiastic please
i'm sorry that's mimosa vermilion she's always been good at recovery and support spells but i hear she's picked up a few
offensive techniques too
she's really talented that's royalty i guess
mimosa please try not to stir up trouble before the exam starts that knight was older than you when you had the audacity to tell him that you can be blunt to the point of being rude sometimes
and you're a bespectacled worrywart so i don't think you have much room to criticize
come on now
and there's klaus lunettes he's gotten a lot more powerful these past few months
the guy's steel magic is practically unstoppable not to mention all the strength training he's been up to
wow look over there it's this year's top newcomer the wind spirit master you know
i'm so mad you promised you'd take me out on a date today don't tell me you don't remember
i promised nothing of the sort are you kidding me all right then tell me we'll go out tomorrow and i might be willing to forgive you
no can't
aww then we better go the day after tomorrow and make it somewhere fancy
i can't make plans that far ahead
you know don't be such a meanie
all right that's it i'm gonna have to mess up your hair
this is quite a lively scene don't you think alectora
i suppose
oh man this place is full of heavy hitters yeah i bet you several members of the golden dawn are gonna make the final cut
the tension in the air here is so thick you could almost cut through it with a knife
it'd be best if everyone relaxed and went with the flow
i don't know i think you might be too relaxed
hey look it's klaus and mimosa long time no see guys
oh hello there asta what a surprise i should warn you i've been training
i'm stronger now so it won't be easy to beat me
that's awesome
whoo now i'm pumped
let's try our hardest today may the best nights win
heck yeah
hey hold on a second your face is all red
you feeling okay
oh yes i'm totally fine thank you so much for asking though
i haven't been this nervous in a really long time
well it looks like you're as loud as ever today
what's up you know
that hot spring trip sure was a lot of fun wasn't it
uh-huh
did you say hot spring
i don't remember you mentioning anything like that
i might have lost the race to the top of the volcano
but i'm not losing anything today got that
i hope you did some mental training for when you fail
don't want you to cry
i won't
great you still haven't told me about the hot spring you know
seems like you're pretty excited about this whole thing
you too asta
won't somebody please explain
ha ha ha ha ha
asta you know you can't forget about me
leo
watch me i'm gonna ace this royal knight's exam
no i am
you wish
you wanna fight about it
i'm gonna pass
oh it's better than you
oh boy i'm so nervous right now
but hey i guess all we can do is give it our best shot right
listen up poser
did i give you permission to wear that black bull's robe
just who do you think you are anyway
probably a fan of ours do you want to spar with me
stop it i'm finral
see i wanted a confidence boost before the exam so i changed my hairstyle
a new look huh there must be something dramatic going on with you then
what's the matter you get your heart broken into teeny little pieces
of course not
yeah right that's silly
you changed your hair every time a woman rejected you there wouldn't be any hair left
on your head for me to cut now would there
that's uncalled for
ahem
actually i was trying to psych myself up a little
say no more
trust me i have just the thing so you can sit back and let me work my magic
oh wait a second i wasn't expecting heavy artillery
anyway i've got a new do and a new attitude to match it so you'd best watch yourself
that good for nothing finral would never come out to a competition like this
how dare you say something so mean about me when you know i have seniority over you
cut it out any idiot could see that this is finral
there's no reason for you to pick on him like that
aww thank you asta
your hair does look pretty tacky though
yeah tacky is a good word for it i mean not only the hair itself but the idea of getting
a haircut to feel better might be the tackiest ever
yep totally tacky and even if it did work i can't think of anything that screams hey look
at me i'm insecure like bright green frosted tips
you guys are just jealous because i have a unique hairstyle that shows off my fun personality
why is those dorks which shut up they're gonna make the whole squad look bad
oh solid it's you
look at that so you've come to disgrace yourself again
i wish you wouldn't because when you fail this exam you'll bring shame to house silva
just leave while there's still time it'll be better for both of us
her magic was refined to an unparalleled degree it was so dignified but despite your royal status
your magic is ugly and coarse work hard improve
sorry i'm not leaving now then if you'll excuse me
that's right i won't be afraid anymore it's time for me to show my siblings how much i've improved
since the last time we met
what a little failure
i'm glad you were all able to attend
without further ado i'd like to commence with the royal knight selection test
allow me to explain the test in detail after all the royal knights will be my warriors will they not
this is a chance to brandish my authority and gain the affection of my people
now this event is a competition of teams
and it shall be called the magic crystal destruction battle tournament
they're putting us on teams there's a crystal
yeah but what are the rules
huh i thought for sure it'd be every man for himself i hope this doesn't turn out to be complicated
the rules are very simple
whichever team is successful in destroying the opposing team's crystal while simultaneously protecting their own crystal from being crushed will be considered victorious
hey that does sound pretty easy i should be just fine
if both of the crystals remain intact at the end of the 30 minute time limit
then the team whose crystal has taken the least amount of damage will be the winner
uh the reason we chose this method was because it
um well
that is
i know it was something good
when facing the eye of the midnight sun it's imperative that members of the different night squads are able to cooperate
he worded that so much better than i could
we feel a team contest is the best way to judge your ability to work with others as well as your strategic proficiency
there's much more to being a royal knight than brute strength
just what i would have said
besides i'll get to observe all kinds of magic not just offensive spells
oh well isn't that clever
i see if we want to be successful we'll have to be able to get along with people from other squads
now then let us reveal the team roster
let's see who am i with
oh sweet i got mimosa
oh gosh am i seriously gonna be on the same team as asta
i mean any other time i'd be happy to spend time with him one-on-one but this is an exam
i'm not sure if i can concentrate and i still don't know what that hot spring thing was about
okay who else it says zerk's lugner who's that
so sorry i'm late for the party everybody
but the wizard king's a reasonable guy so i'm sure he can forgive a little tardiness just this once
who the heck is that
oh me i'm zerk's lugner pleasure's mine
you see i met this elderly woman who was in a sticky situation
naturally as a magic knight i had to step in and offer my assistance cut me some slack
oh dear is that poor woman all right now of course fit as a fiddle
something's not right
stand aside you insolent cur
that's not a very warm welcome what's gotten into you all of a sudden
i'd like to ask you the same question zerk's lugner you say but he's
your majesty
hey who do you think you are
how dare you show up late and with a rotten attitude
the wizard king is one of the few men shara proves of so you better back off
yeah why are you acting like such a bully
settle down folks there's no need to worry
oh all right sounds like you're all pretty fond of this chump aren't you
sorry but i don't really see why he's so great
you guys might be a mindless mob but
not me
that robe it's definitely xerxes
i'll tell you one thing xerxes you really changed your whole look on that long expedition
please don't laugh sir
it's nice to meet you kid
apparently we'll be on the same team
let's keep things friendly
that's the smelliest insect in clover kingdom
they call it a rainbow stink bug
they do
that's because it puts out a rainbow and nasty smells
friendly huh
not the best way of showing it
obviously i was lying
i can't be friends with an annoying hyperactive little pipsqueak
i mean i can tell by that vapid look on your face
you're complete
that really does sting doesn't it
hey
who do you think you are with that
that cool mouth cover thingy
maybe don't compliment him
are you even gonna try to win this thing
it looks like trying is the only thing you know how to do
but didn't you come here for a chance to get into the royal knights
oh hell no
the only reason i showed up was to make fun of all of you
you what
i may not know vice captain xerxes but i didn't think he was like that
all the rumors we heard must have been wrong
everyone calls him the saint of pure ice
but because he's usually posted at the border not many have actually laid eyes on him
are you sure sir
yes
it might prove to be fun
look i'm sorry your majesty
i really don't think i can be on a team with a big mean jerk like this guy
now now you two
you may be different but you're both magic knights
you'll just have to get along
julius
shouldn't i get to say something wise too
all right everybody
i assume you've all identified your teammates
you're kidding
so i have to work with this little punk
i'm not little you're just giant
oh that's it
i'm snapping those ugly glasses in two
i wish you would freak
you better watch your mouth or i'll bury you right where you're standing
hate to break it to you
i'm an earth magic user
you want to bury me go ahead and try it
i swear
men are incredibly stupid
i guess i'll be working with the fussy mage who's always following osta around
huh whatever you're a little bit pretty
but you know his mind do you understand me
keep your hands off of him or else
what are the odds i would end up on the same team as this cocky guy who grew up with osta
are you listening to me
you just keep your distance all right
if you ruin this exam for my yuno then i'm gonna make sure you regret it
okay just leave me alone
i don't believe this
am i really supposed to be teammates with luck the cheery berserker
this should be fun
let's work together and try our best to win okay
what together you say
i suppose
i can already tell you and i are gonna make a really great team
are you okay he's laughing so is he for some reason
yeah i don't know how i feel about this team
well i'm hardly a fan of yours but at least you're reasonably capable
do try to refrain from acting on your own
now that we have our groups let us advance to the testing grounds
well cob will you do the honors please
yes of course yes of course
any course course
whoa he does spatial magic
here we go
everybody's stepping to the portal
so the magic crystal destruction battle tournament or whatever is supposed to happen here
it's huge
this vast and varied environment will be your battle stage
you'll be able to use all your skills to your heart's content
yes sir
the match-ups for the initial round have been chosen by lottery
and organized into the bracketed chart you see here
though winning or losing does not necessarily correlate to being chosen for the royal knights
more victories will increase your favorability
this is an ideal chance for you all to put your talents on display
of course i'd have to face solid first
it'll be such a delight to eliminate you myself
sister
if i win this one
i fight longras next
and the last one i'm up against will be you now
i know i can make it that far
no problem
better yet
i'm gonna win this whole thing
magic knights
it's time to start the exam
yikes
we're in the first battle and everything
attacking your opponents directly is allowed
and although this should go without saying
there is to be absolutely no killing
can i have the spotlight please
we have mages wielding recovery magic standing by for the injured so don't hold anything back
oh hey they brought owen the clever kingdom's number one quack
i didn't know you were going to be part of this exam too doc
my arms are doing a lot better
sorry i didn't mean to worry
yoo-hoo the beautiful babes of the black bulls are here to cheer for our friends
you got this
yay
hey
thank you so much
but shouldn't at least a couple of you guys be holding down the fort right now
captain yami waved us off so i assumed he was fine with him
aww he's so supportive
but that's our captain yami for you
well it looks like we're about to get things started
ah
i see ofta's fighting in the first match
that really does suit his personality don't you think
ofta
you better show these weak losers who they're messing with
oh man damn it
frank
dumb tall people
how am i supposed to feast my eyes and my beloved prince of profession
and i can't see anything
now that the explanations are done i hope our first two teams are ready
oh yeah
i was born ready your majesty
I'll make it true, my soul
My days,この世界に響かせいこう
駆け抜けた日々をいつか誇るまで
僕らなら諦めない
My song, my days
音符を書き加えてく
曲がりくなった道さの暗が
輝ける明日を映すメロディー
ご視聴ありがとうございました
CLOVERCLIPS
1 Hot Spring
What's up, Yuno?
That Hot Spring trip sure was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
Uh-huh
Did you say Hot Spring?
I don't remember you mentioning anything like that
Oh, that's not a very clear response
Or should I assume that it's a secret between you two?
If that's the case, then I have to know
This water's great
Sure is
Soaking in the bath together
Are you itchy anywhere?
I've got a little itch at the base of my right ear
Did I get it?
Yeah, thanks
And washing each other's hair
Could you tell what I just wrote on your back?
Pop potato
You got it
Okay, now draw something on me
And tracing letters on each other's naked backs
What happened?
I need to know
Is Mimosa okay?
All we did was talk about going to a hot spring
And it started making her all weird and lightheaded
She must really love taking baths or something
The competition for the Royal Knights is about to begin
So I, Mimosa Vermillion, will do my best to stay out of the way and not mess anything up
Black Clover, page 74
Flower of Resolution
This flower's getting ready to bloom